pubfilm.ru 2010-07-18

# Ultimate Replicas : Luxury at affordable prices!

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Ultimate Replicas. We are committed to protecting your privacy and encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we protect the information you disclose to us. If you believe that Ultimate Replicas is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, please contact us . 

**Information Collection and Use**  
Ultimate Replicas is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ultimate Replicas collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and financial information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to communicate with the customer. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie from our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. 

**Usage Tracking**  
Ultimate Replicas's database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and # of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests. 

**Aggregate Information**  
Ultimate Replicas uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with partners of Ultimate Replicas to plan advertising or promotions. We do not share any personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
Ultimate Replicas gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. Ultimate Replicas will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested service. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Ultimate Replicas. 

**Catalog, Newsletters, Etc.**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalog, newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and email address to provide these communications. Out of respect for our users' privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below. 

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Security**  
Ultimate Replicas takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information (like your credit card information) online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are fully informed about our security and privacy practices and updated as new policies are added or revised. They are regularly notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure that our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send us an Online Inquiry . 

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for Ultimate Replicas to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources such as our affiliated websites. For example, in order for Ultimate Replicas to enhance our ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our affiliated sites ashford.com, Diamond.com, DiamondDepot.com and 1-888-WATCHES.com. When a user makes a purchase from any of these companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences. 

**Special Offers**  
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice/opt-out below. 

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can be done by using the unsubscribe feature in our communication or by sending us an Online Inquiry . 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

When we update our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated your account, then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices
